https://www.allegrovacuums.com/allegro-central-vacuum-system-privacy-policy.html

Welcome to Allegro Central Vacuums,
Commercial Floor Care Products
more...
Broan
more...
CALL: 1-877-593-2532 | 10AM - 6PM EST MON - SAT
Shopping cart [0]
Cart subtotal
{{total}} USD
Recently added item(s):
Shopping cart is empty
{{item.code}} - {{item.name}}{{item.qty}} x {{item.pricec}} {{item.curr_code}}
Close
Checkout
Product Finder
Enter phrase:
or
Select Filtration:
Washable HEPA
Select Cleaning Area:
3,000 sq. foot
3,000 sq.ft.
6,000 sq. foot
7,500 sq. foot
Select Suction Power:
86 inch water lift
Select Air-Power:
840
Select Motor:
2 Stage, 8.4", Bypass, Tangential Discharge
2-Stage,
Flow-Through
Manual push (no motor)
Single Stage Flow-Through
Select Power Unit Voltage:
~ 220 - 240 v
Select Powerhead Operating Voltage:
-all-
non-electric
~ 110 - 120 v
Select Hose Length:
-all-
12 Foot (3.6 m)
25 Foot (7.5 m)
30 Foot (9 m)
35 Foot (10.7 m)
40 Foot (12.2 m)
42.5 Foot (12.9 m)
50 Foot (15 m)
50 Foot (15.3 m)
6 Foot (1.8 m)
60 Foot (18.2 m)
60 Foot (18.3 m)
7.5 Foot (2.2 m)
8 Foot (2.4 m)
Select Hose Operating Voltage:
~ 110 - 120 v
Select Hose Configuration:
Statement of Privacy
At Allegro Central Vacuum Systems, we are strongly aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we describe to you what information we collect when you register on our website, why we collect it and how we use it to improve your experience. By registering on Allegro website, you consent to the information practices described in this statement.
Use of Personal Information
If you subscribe to our emails or newsletter Allegro may use your personally identifiable email address to inform you of products or services available from Allegro. Allegro may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current products and services. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Allegro blog, this information may be collected and used by others. Allegro does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Allegro will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law.
Security of your Personal Information
Safeguarding information is not 100% secure. Allegro uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Allegro secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Allegro doe not store credit card information on any server.
Changes to this Statement
Allegro will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Allegro encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Allegro is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date below.
Last Update: September 2012
GET NEWESTINFORMATIONAND SPECIALDEALS
READ OURCLIENTSREVIEWS
ALLEGRO CENTRAL VACUUM / USEFUL ARTICLES
BECOME ADISTRIBUTOROR DEALER
Products
Central Vacuum
Central Vacuum Packages
Get In Touch With Us Today!
Type your question here...
Please enter the letters from the image below
